<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shiny on Nouran -Fundamentals of Analytics</title>
    <link>/categories/shiny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shiny on Nouran -Fundamentals of Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/shiny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project </title>
      <link>/2021/06/21/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/21/project/</guid>
      <description>The datasetThe used data set in this project composed of a record of 7 common different fish species in fish market sales. For each fish participated on this record, a certain measurements were taken, which are the fish species, the weight in Gram g, vertical length in cm, diagonal length in cm, cross length in cm, height in cm and diagonal width in cm.
The data was obtained from Kaggle  website, to access the source of the data use the link below</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A05  Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/2021/06/16/a05-exploratory-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/16/a05-exploratory-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>The datasetThe data used in this blog was obtained from The World Bank Data, to access the source of the data use the link below
Link to the data set
Initial Analysis Questions1- which country in North America with the highest population in 2019?
2- which country in North America has the highest population of elderly in 2019?
3- which country in North America has the highest birth rate in 2019?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A04 Shiny App</title>
      <link>/2021/06/11/a04-shiny-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/11/a04-shiny-app/</guid>
      <description>Provisional count of deaths involving coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) by United States countyThe data used in this post is obtained from Data.Gov and it shows the provisional count of deaths involving coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) by United States county.
The dataset is intended for public access and use.
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
